


export const quiz = {

  totalQuestions: 20,
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Question content 1 ?' ,
      answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
      correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Question content 2 ? ',
      answers: ['1', '2', '4', '5'],
      correctAnswer: '4',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Question content 3 ?',
      answers: ['Dubai', 'Algiers', ' :)','123'],
      correctAnswer: '123',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Question content 4 ?',
      answers: ['Den', 'Ma', 'Sep', 'we'],
      correctAnswer: 'MA',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Question content 5 ?',
      answers: ['g', 't', 'u', 'M'],
      correctAnswer: 't',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Question content 6 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Question content 7 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Question content 8 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Question content 9 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Question content 10 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: 'Question content 11 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: 'Question content 12 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: 'Question content 13 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: 'Question content 14 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: 'Question content 15 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: 'Question content 16 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: 'Question content 17 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: 'Question content 18 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    
    {
      id: 19,
      question: 'Question content 19 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: 'Question content 20 ?',
      answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
      correctAnswer: 'f',
    },
  ],
};
